title: Analysis für Informatik - Ableitungen und Integrale
id: 159423406
author: Hendrik Hübner
cards:
- type: markdown
  id: 0  # (generated)
  front: '[$$]\frac{d}{dx}\sin(x)[/$$]'
  back: '[$$]\cos(x)[/$$]'

- type: markdown
  id: 1  # (generated)
  front: '[$$]\frac{d}{dx}\cos(x)[/$$]'
  back: '[$$]-\sin(x)[/$$]'


- type: markdown
  id: 2  # (generated)
  front: '[$$]\frac{d}{dx}a^x[/$$]'
  back: '[$$]a^x \cdot \ln(a)[/$$]'

- type: markdown
  id: 3  # (generated)
  front: '[$$]\frac{d}{dx}\log_b(x)[/$$]'
  Back: '[$$]\frac{1}{x \cdot \ln(b)}[/$$]'

- type: markdown
  id: 4  # (generated)
  front: '[$$]\frac{d}{dx}\left(\frac{f(x)}{g(x)}\right)[/$$]'
  back: "[$$]\\frac{f'(x) \\cdot g(x) - f(x) \\cdot g'(x)}{(g(x))^2}[/$$]"

- type: markdown
  id: 5  # (generated)
  front: Nenne vier Grundlegende nicht elementare Integrale
  back: |+
    - [$$]\\int e^{-x^2} \\, dx[/$$]
    - [$$]\\int \\frac{1}{\\ln(x)} \\, dx[/$$]
    - [$$]\\int \\frac {e^{x}, x} \\, dx [/$$]
    - [$$]\\int \\frac {sin(x), x} \\, dx [/$$]

- type: basic
  id: 6  # (generated)
  front: '[$$]\int \sin(x) \, dx[/$$]'
  back: '[$$]-\cos(x) + C[/$$]'

- type: basic
  id: 7  # (generated)
  front: '[$$]\int \cos(x) \, dx[/$$]'
  back: '[$$]\sin(x) + C[/$$]'

- type: basic
  id: 8  # (generated)
  front: '[$$]\int a^x \, dx[/$$]'
  back: '[$$]\frac{a^x}{\ln(a)} + C[/$$]'

- type: basic
  id: 9  # (generated)
  front: '[$$]\int \ln(x) \, dx[/$$]'
  back: '[$$]x \ln(x) - x + C[/$$]'

- type: basic
  id: 10  # (generated)
  front: '[$$]\int \sqrt{x} \, dx[/$$]'
  back: '[$$]\frac{2}{3}x^{3/2} + C[/$$]'
